One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
I'm too excited to wait for morning to come. (I can't wait)
And so we might as well just grab the sun,
And forcefully drag it into the sky! Go!
That's right, we're Shining! Running! Forever!
Weave the fragments of our dreams together!
When they become one, that will be our treasure!
Let's go Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
D Block's Fiery Start and
the Heavenly Demon's Revelation!
Just die, Rebecca!
You foul blooded wench!
Drop dead, Rebecca!
Today's the day you die!
You're the shame of Dressrosa!
Set her on fire!
That'll make up for her pyromaniac grandfather!
Who cares if she's his granddaughter?
She's got nothing to do with what her grandfather did.
Yeah, that's right.
Despite that cute face, people hate you
even more than Bartolomeo from Block B.
That's true.
That's enough!
Oh, who's entering the ring now?!
What an ill mannered crowd!
I don't even want to look at you!
Have you no shame?
Captain of the Beautiful Pirates,
Cavendish the White Horse makes his entrance!
Cavendish of the White Horse
Cavendish-sama!
Ahh, what beauty!
Hey, get a hold of yourself!
All the ladies in the audience are fainting!
His stunning good looks
have not faded in the last three years!
Cavendish-sama, kill that girl!
Put Rebecca in her place!
Shut up, the lot of you!
I don't know what grudge you have against her...
but this young girl
is putting her life on the line by standing in this ring.
People who don't have the guts to risk their lives
have no right to judge her!
If you want to kill her so much,
then get a weapon and come into the ring!
The shouts of people with no resolve are nothing but background noise!
I entered this tournament for my own reasons,
but I hate these events!
The life of a warrior isn't something to gawk at!
Good work, Farul.
Why did he come here with a horse and a megaphone?
Yeah, you tell them, Cabbage!
Maybe you aren't all bad...
but I still don't like you.
Cavendish-sama!
What a beautiful person!
Who cares about Rebecca?!
We're rooting for you!
Cavendish!
What incredible charisma he has!
He turned a storm of booing into cheers!
Hey, I understand how you feel.
This probably isn't what you wanted, right?
It must piss you off
how easily they change their minds.
The audience are a selfish bunch. Your speech won't really-
I'm so popular!
It makes me so happy!
You're happy?!
It's been three years.
Umm...
Thank you for standing up for me.
Don't mention it. I was genuinely disgusted by them.
You must have it hard.
You don't owe me anything, we are enemies now.
Yes.
That aside, there should be
a reporter or two around here somewhere.
I don't know what I would do
if that got into the newspaper.
Imagine what would happen
if they tried to interview me!
"Hello there, Mr. Superstar!"
I'd be like, "Who's Mr. Superstar?"
Just imagine!
Now, while all that was happening,
all the participants have finished entering in the ring!
Gladiator
Meadows
The Fighting Lion
Pirate
Cavendish
One contender has dropped out, so Block D has 137 participants!
Mummy
The Shaman
Adventurer
Orlumbus
Suleiman
The War Criminal
Squad Captain
Rolling Logan
Gladiator
Acilia
Rebecca
Pyromaniac
Damask
This is a battle royale between these warriors!
It is time for the starting gong!
Now then...
Cavendish-sama!
Decapitate someone, Suleiman!
Get 'em, Orlumbus!
Drop dead, Rebecca!
I hope you're seeing this, Soldier-san.
Dressrosa's Flower Fields
Yellow Kabu and Pink Bee squads have arrived from Green Bit.
Good work, Leo.
The time has come, captain.
This battle is to restore the honor of King Riku, who was dethroned in shame ten years ago,
and to regain our freedom!
I will never forget that man's tyranny
when he came here and stole everything!
We've spent a year preparing for this.
Even if we're up against a Warlord's crew,
we still have a chance!
I'll listen carefully to the plan,
and figure out the best time to run away.
Dressrosa "Acacia"
We have to turn left soon, Zoroland.
Left is the side that you don't have your swords on.
Do you think I don't know left from right?!
Yes!
Your ship is being attacked by
a female commander of the Donquixote Family, Jora.
She uses art to incapacitate her opponents. She is quite a formidable foe.
You know a lot about her.
I know the names, faces and powers of all of the Family's commanders.
Especially the top three commanders who annihilated Dressrosa's army all on their own.
Trébol, Diamante and Pica.
There's no way I could ever forget their faces.
Ten years ago?
Just how old are you?
I'm 27 years old.
T-Twenty-seven?!
That's...
This way!
Zoro-dono! Zoro-dono! Over here!
Hey!
You're being too loud, you idiot!
Who's that? They're acting like they know us.
Swirly-Eyebrowland and Topknotland.
What?!
You're going to save Nami-san?
Then she really is in danger.
No wonder she wasn't picking up the Snail Phone.
Alright, I'm going too!
Wait, Sanji-dono.
We're here to inform Luffy-dono of the situation, remember?
Black Leg.
My precious Violet-chan!
I hope you get passionately stabbed.
Your ship has been captured by Jora.
And now it's headed for Green Bit!
This is so much fun!
Such a beautiful marriage
between the music and art of the ocean! Yeah!
I like the way you talk!
Stop the ship!
You're not heading for Green Bit, are you?!
Law has quite a shock in store for him!
He's expecting you,
but I shall be the one who comes to fetch Caesar!
Brook's acting strange. How could he betray us?
And yet you call yourself a swordsman, Sir Bone?!
I have found myself!
I am an artist through and through.
Creating beautiful art is what I live for!
...though I'm not alive.
Don't bother trying to explain!
These commoners will never understand, Soul King!
Your true passion is for expressing yourself! They can never understand that.
Behold the Art of Life, Dying Art!
Simply exquisite, Jora-san!
Nooo!
Help!
This does not hurt!
You needn't say a thing! I know I have flawlessly portrayed the tragedy that occurred on Dressrosa.
These noisy children should merge completely with the art within ten minutes' time...
and then they shall be silent forever more!
What?!
Brook!
Sir Bone!
Truly amazing! Please let me add some music!
If you would, Soul King.
Could you please restore
my violin and bow, Jora-san?
But of course. Now make me proud, Brother!
Wow! Wonderful!
I'm starting to get sleepy.
I don't want to die!
Look at this, Jora-san.
You see,
the bow of my violin is in fact a sword in a cane.
I hope that it plays exquisite music.
Indeed. You have already been cut.
Hmm? Cut?!
Painting Song: Bamboo Flute Joint Slice!
Bamboo Flute Joint Slice Painting Song
Forgive me. I do not understand art after all.
Flute Joint
Because my eyes are like knotholes!
Knothole
Brook!
Sir Bone!
Green Bit
Long ago...
To be precise, 800 years ago, Law.
Law vs.
Doflamingo and Admiral Fujitora
20 kings from 20 countries
assembled at the centre of the world...
and created a single organization.
That organization is now known as the World Government.
The founding kings brought their families to live in the Holy Land, Mariejoa.
Though the Nefertari family from Alabasta refused
so it was only 19 families...
but those 19 families still live there to this day
and reign over the world.
The descendants of those founding kings are known as the Celestial Dragons.
In other words, 800 years ago
those 19 countries lost their royal families.
Figured it out yet?
Naturally, those countries elected new rulers,
and new royal families were born.
Take Dressrosa for example.
The new royal family here was the Riku family.
Whereas the family who moved to
the Holy Land Mariejoa and founded the Government...
was the Donquixote family.
In front of Dressrosa's Corrida Colosseum
I was worried about Nami-san before you were!
And she obviously would much rather I show up to help her than you!
That's why I'll go!
Fine, just go then.
Kin'emon. This is the map to the Toys' House,
where your friend is being held.
I am most grateful!
Once you find Luffy,
have him contact the others with this.
We have to know what they're doing.
I'm heading back to the Sunny.
So...
how are we gonna get in contact with Luffy?
I do not know,
and that is why we are standing here.
The entire building seems to be tightly sealed off...
I was nearly captured earlier,
so we must avoid drawing attention to ourselves.
I could always cut the entire wall into pieces.
That would definitely draw attention to us!
Then I'll just do it quietly and carefully.
How would that make a difference?
That's the Pirate Hunter Zoro-senpai!
The three-sword-style user whose legend began
when he cut down a hundred men on Whiskey Peak...
and on Enies Lobby
they say he sliced the entire island in half!
And he's been supporting the crew as Luffy-senpai's right hand man!
He's the famous first mate of the Straw Hat Pirates!
He's so freaking cool!
Huh? My tears won't stop...
Dressrosa Royal Palace
Gladius, you really should calm down.
Baby 5.
Do you have any idea how much
that woman's betrayal has messed up our plans?
That damn Violet was supposed to capture Black Leg Sanji and read his mind to learn the enemy's plan.
We were supposed to hinder their plans at every step, and take out every single one of the Straw Hats!
And now look what's happened!
She took out her own subordinates and ran away!
Calm down!
You don't want to explode in here, do you?!
There is nothing I hate more than
people who can't stay on schedule or follow a plan!
Donquixote Family (Pica Army)
Gladius
Anyone who betrays us...
or rather, betrays the young master, must die.
Violet has been acting strange ever since last night.
Just think about it. She could easily have found
the Straw Hats' ship yesterday using her Clairvoyance.
Northeast Dressrosa
Heading Towards Green Bit
Oh, Violet-chan!
You should have waited at the port, as we planned.
That port is already crawling with marines.
You should change your rendezvous point.
I see, so the Navy's here.
They've got a total of four warships here.
So there are at least 3,000 marines
in this country right now.
How did you figure out so much on your own
in such a short amount of time?
Because I have the power of Clairvoyance.
I can send my line of sight flying like a bird
in any direction, up to 4,000 kilometers away.
I can see everything that happens in this country,
without lifting a finger.
So you don't have to worry about me.
I won't get captured.
Does that mean you're staying in the country?
No, don't worry.
I'm going to...
What's wrong?
How horrible! Your ship suddenly reappeared and was struck by lightning!
Lightning?!
Wait, that probably means...
Waters off Dressrosa
Now, what should we do with her?
Sir Bone, I hit her hard.
Indeed, your muscles are well-developed.
R-Really? I have strong muscles?
I don't really want to throw her in the ocean.
Since she's a Devil Fruit ability user.
And I have no desire to see her panties.
W-Who are you calling Miss Universe?
That's not what I said! No one said that!
Should I hit her once more?
Don't bother with her.
We've got to hurry to Traf.
But, what did he mean when he told us to pick up Caesar?
Listen up, you have to...
set sail for Green Bit right now!
I'm leaving Caesar in your care!
Indeed, this is a strange situation.
Since Doflamingo agreed to our demands and threw away his position as a Warlord,
Caesar should be returned to him.
You guys really don't know anything.
There's no way the young master would take some kids' demands seriously.
The young master has not thrown away his position as a Warlord.
Wait, what do you mean by that?
What do you mean?
Ow! That hurts, you little brat!
Onami!
You've all fallen into his trap.
Surely by now, Violet will have exposed all your plans. You can be sure your crewmates have been caught!
Green Bit
Law vs.
Doflamingo and Admiral Fujitora
So you were a Celestial Dragon, Doflamingo?!
Yes, I was.
I'm not a Celestial Dragon anymore.
What do bloodlines and destiny mean anyway?
I don't think there is anyone else in the world who's led a life as checkered as mine.
I'd have loved to talk to you about my life before I met you, over a drink.
But I don't have the time for it.
I have to do something about the
Straw Hat Crew over in Dressrosa.
Many people have made the fatal mistake of underestimating them.
What is it, Fujitora?
Well...
I heard some lightning coming from the sea.
What does the sky look like?
Lightning?
I may be blind, but I thought I could read the weather fairly well.
I guess I'm getting old.
If I remember, Namier could control the weather.
So the ship has come.
Hey Joker, if you've gotten it back, then hurry and give it to me!
My heart, my heart!
Hey, hurry!
I never said that was Caesar's heart.
What?!
That's what you used to threaten me!
Right now, my heart isn't inside my chest!
Hey, what's wrong, get a hold of yourself!
Hey!
A marine's?!
Then where's mine?!
That was my subordinate's scream.
What are you doing, Heavenly Demon?
Room!
You should've paid attention to your gravity, Fujitora.
I'm getting out of here.
Shambles!
Joker, save me!
I didn't think you had this much strength left, Law.
He doesn't know when to give up.
Dammit, let go of me, Law!
Where did you put my heart?!
Quit wasting my time, you brat.
You know there's no place to run.
Can you see Traf?
I can't see very well because of the fog.
Although I do see a strange forest.
If... if Traf's plan failed, and we take back Caesar, what happens?
Doflamingo will target us.
How scary!
What's this?!
What's happening?!
There's something in the ocean!
I-I-It's a school of Fighting Fish!
You came too close to the island!
What are they?
They're killer fish that can sink warships!
Onami!
Follow me, Doflamingo!
If he targets the ship, then we're out.
I'll draw him to the bridge, and then throw Caesar from there.
If I begin a fight with Doflamingo on top of the bridge, I can buy plenty of time for the ship to escape.
What's this?
Are you trying to cross the bridge?
I don't understand.
If you go to Dressrosa, then you're in my territory.
Dammit, those guys...
So that's what you were planning.
Wait, Doflamingo! They have nothing to do with this!
It's over, Law!
Doflamingo's flying toward us!
Young master!
What is this nightmare?!
Are we gonna die?!
No!
Watch closely, Law.
Your allies are going to die a pathetic death right before your eyes!
Stop it!
Traf, hel-
Hey!
Don't come anywhere near my crying crewmates!
Sanji!
Well, here's a strong-looking one.
Translation & initial timing, Yibis
Timing, Galaxy 9000, , Time-checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil, Galaxy 9000, Halee
Soundtracking, Halee
Video editing, Sewil
Raw provider, Crunchyroll
Meadows artist, lord-nadjib.deviantart.com